Nicole Dezoraive

Software Developer

054-6712782 dezoraivenicole@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>GitHub</u>

B.Sc. in Software and Information Systems Engineering at Ben Gurion University.

I am a social activist in the "she codes" organization, and participate in the program in collaboration with the Prime Minister's Office for future engineers who deal with social change.

I have strong work ethic, high self-learning abilities and experience in excellent teamwork in school and at work.

Skills:

Programming Languages and WEB:

Node.js ,Java , JavaScript, Vue.js, CSS, Python.

DB: SQL/NoSQL, MongoDB.

Software and Operating Systems:

IntelliJ IDEA, PyCharm, Jupyter, Eclipse, Visual Studio. **General:** Git, Linux, XML, JSON, OOP, Design Patterns.

Projects:

- Recipes Website: Designed and developed a recipes website full-stack project, including REST API using SwaggerHub and Postman. Back-end written in Node.js and used Azure SQL DB, front-end in Vue.js.
- ★ <u>Search Engine</u>: Developed a search engine in **Java**, which given a document repository and query returns the 50 most relevant documents for that query. Implemented using TF-IDF, Word2Vec and Porter Stemmer algorithms.

Education:

B.Sc. Software and Information Systems Engineering

Ben Gurion University of the Negev - Beer Sheva, Israel.

2017-2022

Experience:

★ Leadership and Social Guidance Coordinator

ISEF Scholarship Education Foundation for academic excellence and social leadership

2018-2022

- Team leader of the 'Bridge to Academy' social project: promoted, helped, and prepared youth to achieve higher education.
- Leadership coordinator for students: delivered lectures, lessons, and tutorials to provide academic and social tools, skills, and guidance.

+ Operations Officer and Commander of the operation room

2013-2016

C4I Corps - Israel Defense Forces, Lieutenant

Responsible for the proper functioning of complex operations while preforming multiple tasks simultaneously and under pressure including handling and solving stressful situations in organized and creative ways.

Volunteering:

'She Codes;' 2021-2022

Women's Technological Community. Responsible for updating the self-learning materials. Now focusing on preparing content for the fullstack course that will open next year.

Languages:

Hebrew - Native

English - Fluent